(Leonard:)Whatcha doin' there?
(Leonard:)Working on a new plan
to catch the roadrunner?
(Sheldon:)The humorous implication being
that I am Wile E. Coyote?
(Leonard:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)And this is a schematic
for a bird-trapping device
(Sheldon:)that will ultimately backfire
and cause me physical injury?
(Leonard:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)What I'm doing here
(Sheldon:)is trying to determine
when I'm going to die.
(Leonard:)A lot of people are working
on that research.
(Leonard:)So what is all this?
(Sheldon:)My family history
factoring in longevity,
(Sheldon:)propensity for disease,
et cetera.
(Leonard:)Interesting.
(Leonard:)Cause of death for
Uncle Carl was KBB.
What's "KBB"?
"Killed by badger."
(Leonard:)How's that?
(Sheldon:)It was Thanksgiving.
Uncle Carl said, "I think
"there's a badger living
in our chimney.